JOJO'S BIZARRE ADVENTURE
DIAMOND IS UNBREAKABLE
These faceless gazes pass by one another
A wound to the heart changes our everyday
Encounters without boundaries
The bizarre is our normal U-yeh
These ordinary mornings,
we're laughing on the surface
Mysteries drawn to each other,
identity still unknown
Without a heads up,
it's quietly lurking somewhere in this town
Although we bicker and complain
In the end, we celebrate
Dancing through the everyday
Crazy Noisy Bizarre Town
EPISODE 3
THE NIJIMURA BROTHERS, PART 1
Yeah. We've taken care of Angelo.
But it'll be a while
till I'm back.
That other photo
we've been looking into…
I'd like you to send it my way.
Yeah, the one the Speedwagon
Foundation obtained in Egypt
ten years back.
I think I might've figured it out.
Later then.
And it's all thanks to him.
Josuke! I killed your grandpa,
but you can't put me to death!
If you kill me, you'll end up
cursed, like yours truly!
Didn't your mommy ever
teach you it's rude to point?
M-M-My hand! My hand!
No one's going to execute you.
Not me or Mr. Jotaro, here.
For you, there will be no execution,
and no incarceration.
Josuke, you handle the rest.
Wh-What the hell you
gonna do, you bastards?!
Enjoy your
eternal penance, Angelo!
Contemplate the life
you took from Grandpa
and everyone else you killed!
Goddamn you!
I wouldn't get too cocky,
little shit!
He'll butcher you both
soon enough!
What? "He"?
You got it.
The one in a school uniform…
The one
who gave me this power.
What?
You don't mean…
You saying there's someone who can
bestow the power of the Stand?
Scared?
Huh? What's so scary bout that?
No… Angelo wasn't born
a Stand user.
No one knew how he
obtained his powers.
But if there's a person
who can impart Stands onto others…
Petrifying, isn't it?
Wanna know more?
It was last year, 1998,
on a night about a month
before my execution.
That night,
I couldn't sleep worth a damn…
I just sat there,
staring off into the darkness.
It was dead quiet.
But then…
in that shitty hole of
a solitary cell,
he was there.
The guy in the school uniform.
The hell!
When'd you get here?!
How'd you get in here?!
Wha…
He was holding
an ancient bow and arrow.
It must've been
hundreds of years old.
Wh-What the hell
are you doing?
I was scared spit less.
My balls hid inside my stomach.
And before I could
let out a scream…
You survived.
Congratulations.
You have talent.
Otherwise, you'd be dead.
You just acquired yourself
a special ability.
Or… perhaps I should say
I extracted it from your soul.
The more wicked the criminal,
the more talent he holds…
A talent a man named DIO once
referred to as a "Stand."
DIO?
Did you say DIO?
Mr. Jotaro?
Is something…
What?!
You fools!
You were so captivated
by my story,
you completely forgot about
my Aqua Necklace!
Angelo, you bastard!
Josuke!
Get me the hell
out of this rock now!
At the moment,
my heart says…
my level of fury
is insufficient.
What're you doing?!
Quit fooling with
your stupid-ass hair!
You're dead, brat!
I said get me
the hell outta here!
My "what"?
Take it easy,
Josuke!
What did you call my hair?
Y-You know…
If you kill me,
the school uniform guy'll
hunt you down!
He lives in this town, too!
What? Josuke, wait!
My level of pissed-off-ness
just wasn't right before.
And I had to turn the dick-wad
into a really great statue.
Good grief.
We needed him
to keep talking.
Huh? You actually
believe all that crap?
It wasn't crap.
He was talking about DIO.
Who is that, anyway?
The Joestars have been fighting him
for over a hundred years.
I, together with my allies,
battled and defeated DIO.
But one thing
remains a mystery.
Why, in 1987,
did DIO suddenly gain a Stand?
So you think that same guy
turned him into a Stand user?
Yeah…
And I think we have
our new enemy.
The school uniform guy.
Or it could be
that bow and arrow.
If it's hiding
somewhere in this town…
Then Angelo was
just the beginning.
Good grief..
MORIOH MUNICIPAL RECORDS
It's like Jotaro said
Something evil is
lurking in this town.
A catastrophic danger is
fast approaching…
No, it's already here.
The number of missing persons
reported in Morioh
has reached 81 this year,
1999, alone.
KIDNAPPINGS AND ABDUCTIONS
HAVE YOU SEEN THIS PERSON?
45 of which were children.
Even if some were runaways,
that's still seven to eight times more
than the national average.
It's an outrageous number.
Not to mention…
Josuke's grandfather…
Hey, Koichi, you're studying
after school's out?
Let's go.
Oh, yeah.
Phew, that's a relief
Josuke seems to be feeling better.
Yo, Angelo.
Uh… Huh? Hey,
was this rock always here?
Yeah, but it didn't look
like this at first.
At first?
Well, okay.
Hi, Angelo…
By the way,
what happened to Jotaro?
Um, he said he needed to
look into something.
He's staying at
the Grand Hotel.
Think it has to do
with this town?
Sure seems like it.
I see.
The crisis facing this town…
Huh? Josuke?
Hasn't this house been
abandoned for three or four years?
Yeah. Can't imagine any one'd
ever buy this dilapidated dump.
Might as well bulldoze it
and build another.
No, someone's living here.
Maybe they just moved in.
I just saw someone
in the window.
Huh?
Nah, that's impossible.
Forget I live
right over there?
I'd notice
if someone moved in.
Besides,
I always see real estate guys
patrolling around
looking out for squatters.
Now that you mention it…
How peculiar.
Maybe I just saw a ghost…
H-Hey,
quit talking like that.
Ghosts spook me out!
Remember, I live right there!
Keep your nose outta
people's business, little brat.
BILLION
Nothing to say?
Koichi!
Hey! What the hell do
you think you're doing?
What? You took the words
right out of my mouth.
You're on my property…
MORIOH LANDMARK 1
ANGELO'S ROCK
ONE MINUTE WALK FROM
MORIOH JOZENJI STREET BUS STOP #3.
ANGELO'S ROCK: TOWN LANDMARK AND
HOT-SPOT FOR ROMANTIC RENDEZVOUS.
FOR YEARS IT'S CHARMED
THE RESIDENTS OF MORIOH,
DESPITE ITS SLIGHTLY
DISTURBING APPEARANCE.
Enough already!
If it's about the newspaper,
I already told you we don't need it.
Who the hell…?!
Look, I just lost
my dad to a stroke,
and I'm still picking up
the pieces, okay?
Come back later, okay?
Y-You're…
Jo…
Joseph!
You finally came back
for me, Joseph!
I've been waiting for you!
I've been so depressed
since dad died!
You came just in the nick of time,
my Joseph!
I love, love, love,
love, love, love,
Sorry to disappoint,
but I'm not Joseph Joestar.
Huh?
Look closer.
See, no wrinkles.
Oh…
Now that you mention it…
You are young!
Good grief…
I'm Joseph's grandson…
Jotaro Kujo.
O-Oh, is that so?
Josuke can fill you in
on the rest.
I can't stand tedious chit chat.
I'm here to see Josuke.
He around?
I said,
where's Josuke?
Huh?
Oh! Josuke still isn't home
from school.
I see…
I'll be back tonight.
Huh?
Leaving already?
Oh…
About your father…
Huh?
It's a shame.
If Joseph Joestar
were here now,
he'd protect you with
every fiber of his being.
But he's an old man now.
I can't let him come here.
I'm here in his stead.
I've got a bad feeling…
That bow and arrow
Angelo was talking about…
And the intel on Enyaba
the Speedwagon Foundation
found in Egypt…
That witch's holding
a bow and arrow
It imparts the power
of the Stand to ordinary people.
This is the last thing we need..
Are you nuts?
NO TRESPASSING
Let him go.
My pop bought this house.
You're not gonna
snoop around here.
Not and get away with it.
You don't quite get it,
do you?
I'm telling you to
let him go, punk.
If you don't,
I'm not gonna be happy.
Hey, now.
"Punk" isn't very nice?
Especially when trespassing
on the property of
a recent acquaintance…
Don't you know
your manners?
I know how to make you
shut that goddamn mouth.
What?!
Bro?!
Interested as to why
I shot him with the arrow?
Because that goon is
Josuke Higashikata.
That so?
So it's him…
He defeated Angelo,
which means his Stand abilities
pose a nuisance to us as well.
You know
about Stands?!
So you two are
Stand users!
Okuyasu!
Make Josuke Higashikata
disappear!
Koichi…
Hmph! I had high hopes he'd turn
into a Stand user,
and a useful one, at that.
Alas, all was for naught.
He's about to
kick the bucket.
M-Move!
I can still heal him
with Shining Diamond!
I don't think so…
Josuke Higashikata!
I, Okuyasu Nijimura,
will make you disappear.
Behold, The Hand!
Get ready!
Get outta the way,
or I'll mangle that ugly mug.
Pretty fast…
Hey, Okuyasu.
It appears
manipulating a Stand is
a lot like driving a car
or motorcycle.
Any bumbling half-wit
can get in the driving seat
of muscle machine.
But he'll still be
too scared to drive!
Bro…
Why'd you have to go and
say mean stuff like that?
This bastard's
faster than I thought.
May I remind you,
this is no game, Okuyasu!
The mere thought of
your Stand, The Hand,
once sent chills down my spine.
Pull yourself together
and wield thy Stand.
Kill Angelo's murderer,
Josuke Higashikata!
He will prove to be
a troublesome one.
I know–
Hey!
I was talking back there!
Th-That's not fair!
Not too bright, are you?
What? Why?!
What makes you say–
I said move.
Koichi!
Thank god.
You're still alive!
Then I can still save…
That's it!
You're not getting away!
I said move!
Get any closer and
I'll really get pissed!
Go ahead and try!
If you've got the guts, that is!
Bastard!
He's got way too much
confidence in his right hand
Shit.
That right hand..
Something tells me… Shit!
Let go of my right hand,
sonuvabitch!
So it is his right hand!
You bastard…
Stay right there,
Josuke!
You can't just leave
your friend behind!
Something's definitely up
with your right hand.
My gut says there's more
than meets the eye.
You can ponder all you want
after you're dead!
This is it!
Koichi.. Hang in there just
a little longer…
That gate…
Something's not right.
NO __ PASSING
No… passing?
I'd stop trying to
back up, prick.
You're moving farther away
from your little friend.
Come a little bit closer!
That's it…
The sign's missing "tres"!
Your Stand's right hand
couldn't have made
part of that sign disappear,
could it?
It cuts out space in midair!
Righto, Josuke Higashikata!
Its right hand makes
disappear whatever it grabs.
But the void left behind…
Closes! Pulling together the space
as if nothing happened!
NO __ PASSING
But the part that my hand
takes away…
Well, I don't have a freakin' clue
where the hell it ends up!
Try to run away,
and I can do this, too.
I grab a little space! And then…
Whad'ya know? You come right to me!
Just like teleporting!
Behold, the Stand that even
my bro fears, The Hand!
You can't run now,
Josuke!
No matter
where you try to hide…
you're always…
within my reach!
Weakling!
That's how you beat Angelo?
Guess you never figured out
how worthless you are.
Not too bright, huh?!
– Now die, Josuke!
– You really are dumb, aren't you?
What?!
That was close.
So that was
Okuyasu Nijimura, huh?
Gotta say,
his Stand was pretty great…
It won't be fun when he
wakes up and tries to attack.
So that he stays napping,
some gentle asphyxiation
should do the trick.
This'll put the sting of
defeat in his soul.
Okie dokie…
K-Koichi!
Now you've gone too far…
I'll kill you!
This arrow is irreplaceable.
There's only one, you know.
It's essential to
my mission.
Losing it is not an option.
Angelo's story says it all…
This is the bow and arrow
that unleashed DIO's Stand
There's no doubt.
It released The World..
After Enyaba's death,
someone nabbed the bow and arrow,
creating more Stand users…
right here in Morioh.
We've got to destroy
the bow and arrow fast…
A villain more horrific than DIO…
A Stand user who wields more
power than The World…
Must never walk this earth.
EPISODE 4
THE NIJIMURA BROTHERS, PART 2